Guide to the Judy Richardson Papers, 1963-2014 RL.10177
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1971-2013; 4 Linear Feet 177 sound and moving image recordings
  - Voiceover and other materials, 1990-2012; 2
    - Laser Surgery, undated; 34
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0013)
    - The Bridge, undated; 36
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0040)
    - The Congregational Library "Journey with Dr. Worthley", undated; 37
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0012)
    - untitled, undated; 38
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0002)
    - untitled, undated; 39
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0005)
    - untitled, undated; 40
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0006)
    - untitled, undated; 41
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0008)
    - untitled, undated; 42
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0010)
    - untitled, undated; 43
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0029)
    - untitled, undated; 44
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0038)